http://www.kistler.com/en/privacy-statement/

ContactLogin SolutionsAutomotive Research & TestVehicle dynamics, durability and tire testingVehicle durability testingVehicle dynamics testingTire testingVehicle safetyTHOR-50M crashtest dummyCrash test dummy systemVehicle crash testing & instrumentationLarge engine monitoringContinuous monitoringOffline ñ engine diagnosticsEngine research & developmentCombustion analysis & cylinder pressure testingMobile combustion analysisMotorsportOptical combustion analysisVehicle NVH (noise, vitration and harshness) testingIndustrial Process ControlIndustrial signal conditioning for smart factoryIndustrial test systemsElectric motor testing for R&DEnd of line test standsMeasuring of connector forcesTactile behaviorSpring testingFriction & efficiency testingCavity pressure measurement in injection moldingInjection molding ñ process controlComposite - process controlServo press | Electromechanical joining systemsAssembly press | Joining modulesProcess monitoring joiningManual presses ñ process monitoringClinching ñ process monitoringSpot welding ñ process monitoringPress fitting ñ process monitoringAssembly ñ process monitoringProcess monitoring formingDeep-drawing ñ process monitoringFracture splitting ñ process monitoringPunching ñ process monitoringFastening technologyBolted jointsProcess inspectionTool testingProcess monitoringCustomized solutionsMedical device manufacturingProduction of plastic medical devicesProcess monitoring in medical device production and testingOptimized semiconductor manufacturing through process monitoringSemiconductor production monitoring through integrated measurement technologyApplications in semiconductor manufacturingTest automationTest systems for continuous materialAutomated testing and sorting systemsAutomated rotary plate testing systemsClocked test systemsTest systems with robot handlingIntegration solutions for test automationSensor TechnologyTest & MeasurementAviation testingHydrodynamic testing solutions for maritime and naval applicationsData acquisition with KiDAQSpace testingWeigh In MotionTraffic data collectionWeight enforcementWeight based tollingIndustrial truck weighingBridge protectionWeigh In Motion servicesSpeed enforcementMobile speed enforcementStationary speed enforcementServicesBiomechanics and force plateSports biomechanicsMotion Analysis & ResearchGait analysisDynamometers for cutting force measurementTool development and tool assessment through cutting force measurementAnalysis of cutting forces and process optimization with dynamometersTool monitoring with cutting force dynamometersThermoacousticsGas turbine monitoringHigh speed dynamicsEnergetic materialsRail technologyBrake force measurementRail Weigh In MotionAcceleration measurementDynamic brake testing and measurement of speedProductsProducts by applicationsCAD CatalogComponentsForce sensorsAccelerometersTorque sensorsPressure sensorsSignal conditioningProducts for the KiDAQ data acquisition systemOptosensors and inductive proximity switchesStrain sensorsSystemsTest data management and data analysisData Acquisition with KiDAQMES SolutionsProcess Monitoring with ComoNeoWeigh In Motion with KiTrafficCombustion analysis with KiBoxWheel Force Measurement with KiRoad PerformanceElectromechanical Joining SystemsMore...ServicesCareerAbout usCompanyThe Kistler GroupThe Management of the Kistler GroupBoard of DirectorsGroup Executive CommitteeValues and VisionsQuality and customer satisfactionSuccess through teamworkCommitted to people and the environmentPassion for technology and innovationLocations WorldwideCorporate Governance and Quality ManagementStandards and CertificationsIntellectual Property RightsAwards and Virtual Patent MarkingHistoryCompetenciesOptimizing vehicle dynamics: sensors and systems for mobility and motorsportFocus on patient's well being: production optimization for medical technologySolutions and expertise for spaceflight programs across the globeAchieving more with the right measurement technology: practical examples, from aircraft engines to NVHThe evolution of the piezoelectric measuring chain: added value for industrial manufacturersAt the forefront of technological development: measurement technology for the 21st centuryFocusing on resource efficiency: monitoring and optimizing large engines with cylinder pressure sensorsBoost efficiency and conserve resources ñ intelligent plastics processing with KistlerHow solutions from Kistler deliver optimized, reliable cutting processesMeasurement technology generates added value: how Kistler supports vehicle developmentMaking sure that if it belongs together, it stays together: fastening technology expertise from KistlerSystematic Weigh In Motion: focusing on automated weighing technologyDTI can do more ñ and advances towards autonomous drivingKistler measurement technology enhances patient safetyEffective production monitoring and quality assurance with KistlerData acquisition of the next generationWith piezoelectric measurement to successReliable, safe and efficient vehicle tests ñ with KistlerPlastics technology: advancing towards Industry 4.0Electromechanical joining systems: an investment in the futureOn the path to success with efficient vehicle developmentJust in Time Production as Competitive AdvantageMedia and NewsMedia ReleasesSuccess StoriesEvents and Exhibitions
Suchen
Home/Privacy StatementData protectionWe appreciate your visit to our website. As you may be interested in buying our products and may need to provide your personal data for possible orders, we would like to first inform you about our activities in the field of data protection.Your data are a sensitive and serious issue for us. By visiting our website, you should not be given the impression that your data is used in a different manner than that which we expressly communicate.The Kistler Group (hereinafter referred to as KISTLER), which comprises Kistler Holding AG and its subsidiaries in Europe, Asia, America and Australia, attaches great importance to the protection of your data. Your data are collected and processed exclusively in compliance with the respective data protection principles. The processing of personal data that are collected when you visit our website is done in accordance with the data protection provisions of the respective country. For example, for Switzerland, we adhere to the provisions of the Federal Data Protection Act ("DSG") and to the provisions of the European General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR").We would like to point out that our website may contain third party links to which our privacy statement does not apply.Below we explain to you the individual concepts (terms) and we explain how they are used.†1) How are your personal data collected?According to Art. 4 of the GDPR, personal data are any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. For example, your name, phone number, address and email address are part of personal data.When you visit our website, our web servers store data on the browser and operating system you use, the website from which you visit us, the websites that you visit simultaneously, the date of the visit and, for security reasons (e.g. to detect attacks on our websites) for a certain period of time, the IP address allocated by your internet service provider.Furthermore, please note that your visit to our website is not associated with automatic storage of your personal data. Your personal data are only collected in cases a registration, an order or other forms in which you can provide your personal information. This means that your personal data are collected only by and with an explicit and active consent.†2) How is your personal data used and disclosed to third parties?Your data is relevant to KISTLER regarding product surveys, newsletters, customer management and marketing. Such data collected by KISTLER will not be disclosed to third parties for their own use, unless we are legally obliged to do so or you have given us your explicit consent to do so. The corresponding consent can be revoked by you at any time according to section 9 of the Privacy Policy.As for the possibility that we have to transmit your data to state institutions due to mandatory national legislation, please note that KISTLER has expressly obliged to confidentiality any recipient who comes into contact with your data or processes them in any way.If you do not want to receive any newsletter anymore, you have the option to unsubscribe from them by yourself at any time. In addition, you have the option of accessing (consulting) the data collected about you and having them deleted if necessary. The exact address for a revocation can be found in section 9 of the Privacy Policy.†3) Surveys and polls concerning KISTLER productsIt may happen that you receive a request from KISTLER regarding a survey about products. The reason for the survey is that KISTLER is very concerned about satisfying its customers and fulfilling their wishes fully and in a customer-specific manner. We point out, however, that surveys or polls are always voluntary and have no impact on any discounts or other special conditions.There is always the possibility to have oneself deregistered from the participation. KISTLER also endeavors to offer anonymous polls so that you can express your opinion in an anonymous form and your opinion can be perceived by KISTLER.†4) CookiesWe use what is known as ìcookiesî when you visit our website. Cookies are small text files that your browser stores. Cookies do not contain any information that could directly identify the individual user. Please note that in such case our website might not work or might not work as intended. For more information about cookies, see our information on cookies.Certain data stored through cookies can be used for advertising purposes, market research purposes or to tailor our offers as required. But the data is always used in line with the legal requirements and in the context of a pseudonymous use.There are various categories of cookies on our website: strictly necessary cookies, functionality cookies, performance cookies and third-party cookies. KISTLER guarantees the flawless and effective use of the website by means of these cookies.In your browser settings, you can always select the option "do not accept cookies". You can also delete previously set cookies at any time. To find out how this works in detail, please refer to the instructions (manual) of your browser or terminal manufacturer. For more information, visit http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager02.html.†5) Web analyticsKISTLER uses the web analytics tool Google Analytics (Google Inc., USA) on its website to draw up anonymous user statistics. Google Analytics uses cookies. Only in exceptional cases, the generated information is processed in the USA. As opposed to Switzerland, there is no equivalent statutory data protection in the United States. To ensure data protection for you, we use a function that only processes the IP address in a shortened form in order to make its relatability to your person impossible.If you have concerns about the use of Google Analytics, you can block Google Analytics e.g. by installing a plug-in in your browser. A plug-in for the most popular browsers can be found here: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.KISTLER uses functions of the Hotjar web service, operated by Hotjar Ltd. Hotjar Ltd. is a European company based in Malta. Hotjar uses cookies. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a server of Hotjar and stored there.You may opt-out of the use of Hotjar. Instructions are available at: https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out.We use the Eloqua service for optimum communication with our customers. The Eloqua servers of the provider ORACLE Germany B.V. & Co. KG, Riesstrasse 25, 80992 Munich are located in the EU. As part of support and administration services, it can not be ruled out in individual cases that individual employees of the Oracle Corporation outside of the EU have also access to user data as part of their contractual service provision. An appropriate level of data protection in accordance with the Federal Data Protection Act has been ensured at the Oracle Corporation. Eloqua places a permanent cookie on the respective login page, unless an Eloqua cookie already exists on your device. If you have already used a website that uses Eloqua, then it is possible that you already have an Eloqua cookie. We might use the Eloqua cookie to analyze your use of our websites so that we can continually improve them. E-mails sent by Eloqua use tracking technologies. We use these data primarily to find out which topics are of interest to you by seeing whether our emails are opened and which links you click on. We then use this information to improve the e-mails we send you and the services we provide, and to connect you to existing tracking or profiling information.If you want to prevent the use of Eloqua cookies on your device in the future, you can do so at the following link: www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/privacy-policy.html#opt-out.†6) Social pluginsKISTLER uses so-called social plugins of social networks, such as Facebook, Twitter and Google+. These are buttons on the KISTLER website. When you visit the website, these buttons do not send data to the respective social networks automatically. Only when you click on the button a direct connection with the server of the respective social network is established and the network can collect data and set cookies.If you are simultaneously logged in to a social network, the social network can allocate your visit to this website to your user account.KISTLER has no influence on the extent of such data collected by social networks. For more information, please refer to the provisions on your rights and the setting options to protect your privacy at the respective social networks.If you are a member of one of the following social networks and you do not want the respective provider to collect data, relating to you, through our website and to link it, in some cases, to other stored data, then please completely log out of the respective social network before you visit other websites and, where appropriate, also delete the corresponding cookies.KISTLER uses the following social plugins:Linkedin Inc. (linkedin.com, LinkedIn Headquarters 2029 Stierlin Ct. Ste. 200 Mountain View, CA 94043, USA);YouTube Inc. (youtube.com, YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave, San Bruno, CA 94066, USA);Xing AG (xing.com, Dammtorstraﬂe 30, 20354 Hamburg, Germany);Facebook Inc. (facebook.com, 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA);Twitter Inc. (twitter.com, Headquarters, 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA);†7) Job portalApplicants can apply at KISTLER by e-mail with their application documents. After a rejection, these application documents are kept by KISTLER for a certain period of time to check whether a former candidate is not suitable for a future job. Such documents are always treated confidentially by KISTLER.At any time, you have the option to request KISTLER to delete your application documents. KISTLER will endeavor to delete the application documents as quickly as possible.†8) Security and confidentialityWe use data networks that are protected, inter alia, by industry-standard modern firewalls and password systems to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal data we collect online. Adequate measures are taken when handling your personal data. Such measures protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.†9) Information, correction, deletion and contactWe draw your attention to the fact that, as a visitor to our website, you have the right to be forgotten, i.e. that you can request the deletion of your personal data. Again, KISTLER will do everything to delete the data within five business days. You also have the option to revoke any processes at any time.We are always at your disposal for questions on data protection, revocation or deletion of personal data. You can reach us at:†data-protection(at)kistler.com†10) ChangesThis Privacy Statement may be changed from time to time due to any changes in case law or applicable legislation. Possible changes will be always published on our website.
Contact
QuotationProduct informationServiceMediaJobsFurther information
Mr.Ms.
AbkhaziaAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Costa RicaCÙte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIran, Islamic Republic ofIraqIrelandIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (North)Korea (South)KosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRÈunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab Republic (Syria)Taiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
I'd like to receive important news and product information.
I accept the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.*
I agree with my entry into the register of job-seekers of the company group KISTLER
Send
© 2020 Kistler GroupGlossarySitemapImprintKistler Instrument Corporation Terms and Conditions for Sales and ServicesTerms of use for Kistler.comPrivacy StatementTerms & Conditions of PurchaseCookies Kistler USA Kistler Instrument Corp. 30280 Hudson Drive 48377†Novi, MI United States †+1 248 668 6900
Contact us
Locations Worldwide Join us on social network
NewsletterKeep up to date conveniently by newsletter.
Submit
Newsletter Subscription Mr.Ms.
I'd like to receive important news and product information.*
I accept the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.*
Sign up Thank you for your interest!Thank you very much for your interest in our products and services.Please check your mailbox and follow the link in the confirmation e-mail to confirm your subscription.
